https://townoforangepark.com/privacy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footer
Search this website
You are here: Home / Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Primary SidebarHome
Town Manager
Town Council
Town Clerk
Departments
Community Calendar
Job Opportunities
Purchasing Opportunities
Important Documents
F.A.Q.’s
Special Events
Town History
Footer The Town of Orange Park ensures freedom from discrimination because of race, color, religion, sex, national origin, age, handicap, or marital status.
Anyone with concerns about discrimination, or requests for special accommodation or translation services should contact the Town Clerk at (904) 264-9565
This institution is an equal opportunity provider and employer.
Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public-records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.
